[{"answer": "Well, right now Piers, it is 4 a.m. local time, and despite that there are still thousands of people here occupying Independence Square and they're all busy working one way or another.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Phil, what is the latest going on in Kiev right now?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "So it started a few months ago when the Ukrainian government decided at the last minute that it would not pursue a closer relationship with Europe and instead wants it to favor its relationship, its historic relationship with Russia and rebuild that relationship, move the economy closer to Russia again.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "And Phil, and it's hard for viewers who are not perhaps completely savvy with what is happening here, what is this conflict about?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "Well, sure, they are parallels but one is much more long-term than the other.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "What is going on in both these countries?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Are the Egypt people better off or worst off because of the Arab Spring uprising?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Let's take a look.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "What can I do?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Everyone was there.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What was it feel like backstage last night?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "And -- yeah, she's a different Lady Gaga.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "You mean when they used to attack me?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "But I have tremendous respect for the fact that he not only is as a president, I have respect for the fact that he is trying to execute what he truly believes are the right thing for the country which I think is absolutely the wrong thing for the country.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "ORGAN: But he's a man of principle in that sense?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I suspect he won't be around for the next reappearance.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Shouldn't GOP party candidate, a long standing party member like Abbott, should he be having someone like Ted Nugent around him if he's going to be saying stuff like this?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, the gun is a major issue if it's -- it has to be handled the right way, its got to be controlled in the right way.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "At what point does the gun itself not become a major issue?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "IULIANI: Well, you change the culture by changing the way people behave not necessarily by the gun.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "How do you change that culture?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, just to talk about what you were saying earlier, it is incredible.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "I asked Rudy Giuliani earlier, are the Egyptian people better off or they're worst off because they've got spring up rising, what do you think?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, if you see the film, you see the characters who are struggling for change in Egypt.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "How does things have improved, have they moved on?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, Ahmed Hassan (ph) is in the film.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Is there a great leader in Egypt right now that you can say in 20 years time it was that person, man or woman who led this for us?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's exactly right.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "A victory, I guess, the Oscars just gives you a huge global platform to share the message of the film, right?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, it's because everyone always said that I looked bad and I started to believe so I didn't like the way I looked.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "You were unhappy with the way you looked, why?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Yeah, at my school.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "And you were being bullied by other kids?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "They were just laughing behind my back all the time and they said, \"Oh, that's the girl with the big nose.\"", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "What were they saying to you or how are they bullying you?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I felt very sad that she was going through what she was going through.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "How do that make you feel as her mother?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you understand the argument against it?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Well, and you don't charge for this kind of surgery, right?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "I felt pretty good about myself like I felt like I was a normal kid again and I could actually look at myself without wanting to cry.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Renata, how did you feel after you have the surgery and after everything had calm down and you were back to normal but looking different and you looked in the mirror, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Yeah Piers.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "You also doctor, I mean, you encouraged a certainly further step in having some chin surgery as well so that her face would look consistent as I would describe it or?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "It is a question of degree, because again, what we do as a foundation, as a surgical foundation, is we take children with mild, moderate, and severe birth defects and they go through our system of being approved by a group of physician...", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Is it just a question of degree?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, they have to academically be on a certain age that is acceptable for any kind of surgery like this.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What is your view for this kind of age and they want that?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, ethical...", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Do you have any personal ethical issue about people who just want a slight correction to look a little bit prettier rather than a genuine problem like Renata had?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I felt like -- in the end, I'm the one who wins here and not the bullies because they don't have any effect on me anymore.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How do you feel about the people who bullied you?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I feel like he's a great doctor and this foundation is amazing.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "And how do you feel towards Dr. Romo?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "I'm very thankful that this foundation is able to help children like Renata and other kids without -- without their help, we're now never would have received the help that she has received", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What do you feel about all of this?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "It's very contentious issue, plastic surgery isn't it?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "ORIZKOVA: Yes and no because it's -- I don't think it's so much supermodel driven because there's not even really supermodels that are around anymore.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Do you think pressure on young women today is being driven by the whole supermodel era and the fact that most models these days are pretty skinny and look a certain way?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "No, but she's so interesting and there's so much life and talent behind that mathematics of her face.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "She's not practically beauty at all, right?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "No, actually it wasn't anything like that.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "You look at them and you thought you know what, the rest of you suck, right?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes 30 none of -- not of marriage but 30 since we meet.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "30?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "God, you know, I do get that question a lot and I think it's unfortunate that it's really just a question of luck finding the right person at the right time.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What has been the secret?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "It's huge because they put the music to that harrowing footage from Africa.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "And you remember we could be in English, you remember it from Live Aid, right?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I am passionate about writing.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What, for you, the most passionate about these days?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Is this your serious look, isn't it?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I'm prepared to make an effort for you.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "You can sing?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "John Cleese was one of my first guys I had a crush on.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Brilliant.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "John Cleese, with the Silly Walks?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "You know, I cried.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "How did you feel when you -- when (inaudible) to winning?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "For sure, you know, when I was looking at on the last year or so, it's how to improve, you know, how to become a better father, a better husband, and then at the same time, golf, a better golfer and so you have to find balance and so over the last three years, I felt I found some balance.", "docId": "140218pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Does that going forward now really embolden you to go maybe win the Masters again?", "qSentId": 593}]